It is nice with chickens in the garden, it is a bit the picture you have of the countryside.
There are several advantages to the chickens going out in the garden.
First, it is the well -being factor.
Not only for me, that I think it is nice that there is life in the yard.
null
But also for the hens.
They enjoy walking around and picking.
And they are happy to crawl into the bush.
And that one has advantage number two:
They clear weeds
As an example, they are particularly fond of cherries.
As it puts in with good appetite.
The third advantage of chickens in the garden is that it reduces feed consumption.
Not just that they feel comfortable and that they jaw weeds.
Without the weed they do not have to give as feed.
They eat less in the summer when they have access to insects and weeds all around.
So there are of course disadvantages too
It is not only me and the hens who think it is nice with chickens in the garden
So do it two others
It's the day eye:
And the night eye fox
I have had total since I move out to the yard
So have got rid of
Four chickens to the hawk and
null
a rooster to the night eye
The fox
That has arrived in the evening
null
I have my own theory
I think the hawk is the worst in the autumn
That's why I take the chance now and let them go free during high summer
All the chickens I got rid of it have been during high season or during the fall
When it has been declined and they have not had so good places to hide on
Now they usually live under bushes and so on so I think the hawk is a less risk now.
The fox is another thing.
After all, it is mainly night -active.
Hens are not looking for weeds, they are looking for food
It means
Kirskånen - There we agree both to me and the hens.
But they do not jaw nettles
They don't chew thistles
Without it, the tasty things they put in
And what they put into themselves may be the one that I want to have left
Like that it is
Completely hopeless if you get the hens into a salad land
They love salad
The same thing my berry bushes
Should you submit her
She comes out with the eggs and then you take them away from her.
Replaces it to something good
It works just fine
A possible problem can be even if you live in densely populated area
null
Partly because the neighbors can complain about a rooster that sounds
There is not much to do about you avoid having a rooster.
I have two pieces but I'm not disturbed by the roosters
I don't think the neighbors do either
I have my cocks here and
The neighbors 500 meters in that direction also have rooster and they also have rooster too
When any of the roosters start gala, the other roosters respond
I think it's pretty homely
The advantage of living like this in the real country there too
There is plenty of room for the chickens
null